<resources>
    <string name="app_name">To-Do</string>
    <string name="text">E-learning (or Distance Education) is a recognized educational practice that supports a flexible model of access to knowledge, enabling education and training numerically larger audience than what is traditional education models can effectively support (Som Naidu, 2006). As the years go by, ways of learning is changing modified and adapted to suit the trends and the requirements of the era. "The success of Web 2.0 inspired e-learning to evolve into e-learning 2.0, which exploits the collective intelligence to achieve education-centric user" (Huang Shiu, 2011). Teachers are still necessary for students and always will be, but the fact that e-learning is now widespread and very helpful for students cannot be overlooked. Therefore e-learning is being changing modified and adapted as expected. The distances are no longer any an obstacle to someone who want to study any science up to a point. Nevertheless in some cases the use of e-learning requires some initiation/training in order to achieve familiarization on these. As any product or service, thus e-learning acquired some standards which consist of some specific criteria in order to ensure quality of service and customer satisfaction. Apart from the criteria that must be met by each e-learning platform to ensure quality, some issues of a new kind of e-learning named Adaptive Learning will be discussed, which attempts to reduce some disadvantages of the classic e-learning models. Adaptive Learning Systems (ALS) that are based on Web (Web-based Adaptive educational Systems) are development of two earlier types of ILS (Intelligent Learning Systems) (E.Wenger 1987) and AHS (Adaptive Hyper-media Systems) (P. Brusilovsky,1996). The classic learning models that we knew so far have several disadvantages which attempt through adaptive learning to reduce. One of these is the disorientation and cognitive overload.

The adaptability in an educational system aims to support the learner during the study, giving the system the ability to be dynamically adjusted depending on the learner and its evolution according to student preferences. On the other side, it is extremely difficult to understand the learning preferences of students and adapt the method to deliver content according to the learning styles of students and this is one of the several problems that ACLs have to face (Dekson D.E. et. Al 2010).

Additionally, the goals of the learner, background, experience and preferences are characteristics that differentiate users on a system, while considered particularly significant enough to affect the learning effect. Particularly in case where people are adults, who often have specific opinion about their needs, their participation in the formation of content of their training helps the acquisition of knowledge.</string>
</resources>